uux.fr 2018-08-30

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains in general terms how we protect the privacy of your personal information. It will apply to any personal information you provide to us when registering with us.

 What Information Do We Collect?

The types of personal information that we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and on the type of service you request from us. For example, when you wish to purchase a product from this website we may collect details such as your name, e-mail address, shipping address, billing address and other information relevant to your purchase.

 As we are required by law to obtain your consent to the collection of "sensitive information", we will assume that you have given consent to the collection of all information you have provided to us for use in accordance with this Policy, unless you tell us otherwise.

 How We Collect Information

We may collect personal information about you when you visit our website, when you deal with us through our website, or when you have contact with us in person. We will not collect any personal information without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the fields necessary to facilitate a transaction through this website.

 How We Use Your Personal Information

We generally collect your personal information for the following purposes:  
1\. To facilitate your access to our website, products and services   
2\. To deliver products you have ordered from us   
3\. To provide you with information about our products and services   
4\. To seek your opinion on our products, services, marketing and website.

 Some of the personal information we collect is essential for us to be able to accurately identify who is using the service. Other types of personal information we collect help us to develop a profile of who is using our service and what their interests are. This assists us in offering products to suit the needs of the users of this website.

 Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We may disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose for which the information was collected or for related purposes, for example to complete a transaction on your behalf or provide you with a product that you purchased. We engage third party contractors to perform services for us which involves the contractor handling personal information we hold. For example, we currently engage third party contractors to:

 1\. Deliver products purchased from this website   
2\. Provide electronic funds transfer services, credit card account processing and related services

 Security of Your Personal Information

We will securely hold your personal information and we will not trade, rent or sell it. We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you. Personal information may be stored both electronically on our computer system. Firewalls, passwords, anti-virus software and email filters acto to protect all our electronic information.

 Changes to This Privacy Statement

We may amend this Privacy Policy as our business requirements or the law changes. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be updated on our site, so please visit this page periodically to ensure that you have our most current privacy policy.

 Resolving Your Concerns

If you have any query on how your personal information is collected or used, please feel free to contact us. We will respond to your query or complaint as soon as possible.
